# Muhammad Nabeel Amin

nabeelofficial70@gmail.com/+923214382188/chack number 70 rb bandalla kalaan, Faisalabad, Punjab, Pakistan, Faisalabad, Punjab

#### Education

## **Bachelor of Computer Science**

Government College University, Faisalabad • Faisalabad, Punjab 09/2021

CGPA: 3.23 / 4.0

# INTERMEDIATE (I.C.S)

Government Degree College, Khurrianwala, Faisalabad • Faisalabad, Punjab 04/2017

MARKS: 698 / 1100

### Matriculation (Science)

Al-Abbas High School & Colleges, Khurrianwala, Faisalabad • Faisalabad, Punjab 07/2015

MARKS: 657 / 1100

# Summary

I've 2 years of experience in tech industry and also in Textile industries. These whole years of experience have made me the most exceptional and demanding one. I genuinely express the intensive skills every firm wants. Skilled Coding Teacher teaching at elementary and middle school levels. Also has 2 years of Freelancing experience as a Software developer.

#### Skills

- JavaScript
- · MY SQL, MongoDB
- Microsoft office
- WordPress

- · HTML5, CSS3
- · Customer service
- : Git, GitHub
- Teaching

- Elementor
- Divi
- : Communication skills
- Freelancing

### Experience

# Coding Teacher

Air Class(China) • Remote(part-time) 11/2020 - Present

- Evaluate and document student progress
- Set up creative learning environment for 200 plus students
- · Communicate clearly with administration and parents on student accomplishments/struggles

### Web Developer

Fiverr • Faisalabad, Punjab

Designed and developed efficient and maintainable software according to business objectives and needs of various clients.

Here is the link of my profile:

https://www.fiverr.com/users/muhammadnabe182/

### Computer Operator

J.K Textile Mills Sheikhupura Road Faisalabad • Faisalabad, Punjab 10/2021 - 03/2022

Managing and handle system software and reviewed personnel records to determine names, rates of pay, occupations of new hires and changes in wage rates. Doing data entry related tasks.

### Full Stack Web Developer

Up work/Self-Employed • Faisalabad, Punjab 01/2021 - Present

Designed and developed efficient and maintainable software according to business objectives and needs of various clients.

Here is the link of my profile:

https://www.upwork.com/freelancers/~01c757fb6e43b08e88

#### SOFTWARE QUALITY ASSURANCE INTERNSHIP

Afiniti Software Solution • Faisalabad, Punjab 07/2020 - 09/2020

Testing New Software for company in this internship Remote/Online.

### Web Development Intern

NFC Institute of Engineering and Fertilizer research, Faisalabad • Faisalabad, Punjab 12/2019 - 08/2020

Web Developer Training Under Government Of Pakistan Training Program at NFC university Faisalabad

### Internship Student

Bright network, UK • Faisalabad, Punjab 05/2020 - 07/2020

Create a facial recognition system with agile methodology

### Time Keeper

J.A Textile Mills Sheikhupura Road Faisalabad • Faisalabad, Punjab 10/2018 - 08/2019

Managing and handle attendance system software and reviewed personnel records to determine names, rates of pay, occupations of new hires and changes in wage rates.

Languages

• English • Chinese • Urdu • Punjabi